<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on</title><link>https://docs.fabulous.dev/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.fabulous.dev/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fabulous for Xamarin.Forms</title><link>https://docs.fabulous.dev/about/fabulous-for-xamarinforms/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.fabulous.dev/about/fabulous-for-xamarinforms/</guid><description>Never write a ViewModel class again! Conquer the world with clean dynamic UIs!
This library allows you to combine the power of functional programming and the simple Model-View-Update architecture to build any kind of mobile and desktop applications with an expressive, dynamic and clean UI DSL. Go cross-platform and target iOS, Android, Mac, WPF and more!
Fabulous for Xamarin.Forms is build on Fabulous, which aims to provide all the tools to let you create your own mobile and desktop apps using only F# and the Model-View-Update architecture (shorten to MVU), with a great F# DSL for building dynamic UIs.</description></item><item><title>Fabulous.StaticView (deprecated)</title><link>https://docs.fabulous.dev/about/fabulous-staticview/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.fabulous.dev/about/fabulous-staticview/</guid><description>Write cross-platform apps with Xamarin.Forms, using MVU architecture and static XAML UI
In some circumstances there are advantages to using static Xaml, and static bindings from the model to those views. This is called &amp;ldquo;Half Elmish&amp;rdquo; and is the primary technique used by Elmish.WPF at time of writing. (It was also the original technique used by this repo and the prototype Elmish.Forms).
&amp;ldquo;Half Elmish&amp;rdquo; is a pragmatic choice to allow, but doesn&amp;rsquo;t provide the same level of cognitive-simplicity.</description></item><item><title>They use Fabulous</title><link>https://docs.fabulous.dev/about/they-use-fabulous/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.fabulous.dev/about/they-use-fabulous/</guid><description>Tawasal # Website | Google Play Store | App Store
Description # Tawasal is a secure multi-purpose messenger and superapp, offering free voice, text, videoconferencing and lifestyle services to clients around the world. Tawasal introduces a full suite of exciting features with something for everyone, from live sports, text, broadcasts and giveaways, to payments and news services.
Why they chose Fabulous? # Our team at Tawasal was looking for cross platform solution that was stable &amp;amp; supported.</description></item></channel></rss>